Extend arms and bend wrists
at precisely 90 degrees,
making sure to keep each finger straight.
Then palms up in front, straighten elbows,
whilst maintaining the 90
degree angles, bend each finger.
One, two, three, four, five.
Now open your hands back up.
And done?
Now you are ready to draw manga.
Let's begin, shall we?
Thank you.
Let's talk about your summer
deadline, Rohan-sensei.
I hope you haven't forgotten about
the 45-page one-shot, do you?
Have you at least settled on a story yet?
Hmm. One moment.
A solar eclipse might be
a good theme. Oh, yeah!
That's an amazing hook! I love it!
But you know what else sounds cool?
What if you drew for us a manga about buying
a beautiful holiday villa in the hills?
Sorry, come again?
It doesn't look like you're into the idea.
That's such a shame.
Now you hold on just a minute.
I need you to explain what you
meant by a villa in the hills.
It was an idea for a story,
but like you could also
totally go and do it for real
and see if maybe a bolt of
inspiration strikes you.
Enough!
Stop acting like you
don't know what I mean.
I took issue with the buying
part of what you said.
You know full well that
I recently declared
bankruptcy due to a purchase
of that very nature.
Rohan Sensei, I don't want anything
from you other than a good story.
Here, look at this.
Quite the discovery, huh?
It's a little village nestled in
the hills with no connecting roads.
And yet it's got about
a dozen luxury villas.
I bet you never would
have guessed there was a
place like this just a few
hours northwest of Morioh.
It's so weird seeing
such a developed patch
of land without any roads or power lines.
They're not hooked up to a power
grid or any other public utility.
Yet they've got working
electricity and transportation.
Judging from all those helipads,
I'm going to assume that these
people get around mainly by air.
You may be right.
It certainly seems like
they can afford it.
And is it me, or does that building by
the tennis court have an Isetan logo?
Wow, it does!
They have one there?
Good for them!
Oh, and one more thing.
At the moment, one of those
villas is accessible to you.
That's right, for three million yen.
So, you finally admit you're
selling me real estate.
Still wrong. Trust me.
The only thing I want you to do is draw.
The one buying a house will be me.
You? Now let's see.
That's 2,600 square meters
going for 3 million yen.
On my salary, I could probably get a
loan for it or even buy it outright.
Yeah, this could work.
I could commute from my
apartment during the week,
then retreat to the countryside and kick
back during the weekend and holidays.
Slow down for a sec.
You forced me to ask.
Is this coming out of your pocket
or from the publishing company?
I was planning to do
this with my own money.
So I'm to draw a manga about you.
Nope, once again, this is
all to inspire you, silly.
Look, I've put a lot of thought into this.
And I'll share with you all
the info I dug up to prove it.
The owner of Villa No.
1 is the president of
a shipbuilding company.
No.
2 belongs to a pharma CEO.
While the guy in No.
3 owns a printing company.
And the guy in number four
runs a cosmetics business.
Needless to say, all the people living
here are fancy-pants millionaire types.
With their trophy wives and cute kids?
Sounds like a dream, doesn't it?
Collecting data is one thing, but
making sense of it all is quite another.
For starters, how does a villa
here go for only three million?
There must be a catch.
Except there isn't, Rohan-sensei.
I've yet to tell you the most
important thing about this place.
The 11 people who live here
they all bought their lots
when they were just 25 years
old can you Believe it I mean
yeah they're super loaded
today but all of them came up
from humble beginnings The
most recent arrival in this
village bought his plot of
land number 11 back in 1989
the man Was a modest 25 year
old delivery driver who had
moved all the way out there
from tokyo And now he's the head
honcho of a big airline company
worth over 30 billion yen
So yeah, there's not a single person
living in this village who came for money.
They were all just ordinary
25-year-old dudes who moved
out here one by one and built
up their fortunes over time.
And you've probably noticed, but it
looks like there's a common number.
As it happens, I'm also
25 years old. Get it now?
There's clearly a story here.
Now be honest, don't you want to come
see me get a lucky villa of my own?
I'm assuming you have access to a chopper.
I can't see how else we'd get there.
Rohan Sensei, there's one more important
detail I forgot to mention earlier.
The seller is the head of the village
council, and they're very fussy about decorum.
I've heard they're dead set
against selling their land
to anyone whom they think
comes across as disrespectful.
Proper manners will make
all the difference today.
So, I hope you'll be
on your best behavior.
I fail to see how my conduct will endanger
anything when the only buyer is you.
Okay, fine.
I'll just spell it out for you.
It doesn't matter which one
of us commits the faux pas,
they'll just lump us together
and toss us both out.
And I don't want to leave
empty-handed after that hike.
Seriously, though,
I don't know if anyone's
ever told you this before,
but you always act like some hotshot diva
who's addicted to his own flatulence.
Oh, come on.
What does that even mean?
It means stop worshipping
yourself and be a good boy,
or the locals will boot us before
you can smell one more fart.
Here's an idea.
Let's practice before we go in.
Traditionally, where in the house
should a visitor take their jacket off?
You seem set on wasting my
time with this nonsense.
The answer is at the entrance.
Not once you've come inside?
But before you pass through the door!
just in case there's
lingering dirt on your coat.
What a relief!
So you do know how to behave!
Wait,
I understand this visit takes precedence,
but perhaps we should
do something about that.
I mean that chick over there.
Poor thing.
The simplest explanation would be
that it fell down from its nest.
What should we do?
If we leave him, he might
get eaten by something.
Or freeze to death.
Well, if that happens, we could
simply write it off as nature's work.
Good thing we found you, little Fool.
Don't worry, we'll help you.
I'm glad I hung on to
this box. There you go.
It's likely his nest is
in one of these trees.
We should come back
here later and find it.
Good day to you.
I'd like to begin by thanking
you for coming all this way.
And I'm glad to see that good weather
was accommodating to your long journey.
This way, please.
We've been waiting.
Let us proceed swiftly.
My name is Kyoka Izumi.
Thank you so much for sparing
us some of your precious
time to discuss the sale
of your lovely estate.
This gentleman here is my
good friend Rohan Kishibe.
He's a successful manga artist.
I'm pleased to meet you.
You may call me IQ.
I've been given the great honor.
of facilitating your visit today.
Please follow me as I guide you.
Now then, if you would kindly allow
me to relieve you of your coats.
Please, you may enter at your leisure.
Hey!
In just a moment, I shall go fetch the
seller with whom you will transact.
Make yourselves comfortable.
I'm beginning to suspect that the test
has already been put into motion, right?
I'm talking about our etiquette.
There may be rules
surrounding tea drinking,
and they're waiting to see
how we approach our cups.
Somehow, I get the feeling
we're being observed right now.
Do you know the proper way of proceeding?
Or should I just go straight
to consulting the internet?
No, it's fine.
As the buyer, I should
be able to handle this.
Don't trouble yourself.
Everyone knows the polite way of drinking
is quietly and without acting weird.
Excuse the intrusion.
I sincerely regret to inform
you of this, but sadly,
the seller is no longer
interested in meeting with you.
I must ask you to leave the premises now.
It pains me to say it, but we cannot
abide your etiquette mistakes.
Miss Izumi.
We have no land to sell to
anyone who lacks manners.
Please return home for today.
Wait, what are you talking about?
What did I...
What did I do wrong? Firstly,
though you are a guest in this house,
it is improper to take the
furthest seat from the door!
unless it is offered to you.
You should take the closest.
You are expected to remain there until you
have been properly greeted by the host.
Secondly,
it is improper to tread on the edges
of the tatami mats in a Japanese room.
And third,
when sitting at a table lower
than the level of your knees,
it is correct to hold
your tea by the saucer.
However, to put your finger through the
handle of the teacup is unspeakably vulgar.
Good etiquette is a simple organization
of shoulds and should-nots.
There is no gray area.
Again, I must ask you to return home.
You mean we're finished already?
Wait a moment. Please.
You said it's just for today, right?
Does that mean it'd be
possible for me to try again?
Because if it does, I'd
sincerely appreciate it.
I'll give it this time. What?
Just one more try.
If it's not too much to ask, I
promise I won't disappoint you again.
Please let me prove it.
So you would like to attempt
the trial one more time.
Did I understand you correctly?
Only if that's okay.
Very well, then.
If that's the case, I will present your
request to the Master for an answer.
Thank you. Please do.
I promise you won't regret it.
Hey, let's just leave.
There aren't any good manga
ideas to be found here.
I would leave if I weren't
so in love with this place.
Sure, they're strict about etiquette,
but that's what I'd expect
just just look around you.
It's so lovely
Hi, Kyoka speaking
What the hell happened?
Oh, no!
No, please, no!
I have to...
I just got news my mother was killed.
They said that she...
There was a car accident,
and she didn't make it.
My boyfriend was there, too.
We were making plans to
finally get married next year,
But he was in the car with
my mother at the time.
Then she suddenly got a
heart attack at the wheel.
I can't...
They've both been taken from me!
What is going on?
Where did these insects come from?
Excuse the intrusion.
The Master has agreed to let you
take the trial of manners once again.
Now let us proceed.
You will reveal yourself this instant!
Heaven's door!
I am the guide at the main gate,
and the land speaks through me.
When crossing into this domain,
those lacking proper
etiquette will soon find
themselves also lacking
something that they cherish.
Without exception, this is
the punishment of the hill.
One will gain, or one will lose.
That is the fundamental rule
which governs this land.
Those proficient in
etiquette will gain success.
Those who are not will
suffer for each offense.
This young man is no stand user.
It seems he's little more than a
guide and mouthpiece for these beings,
with no special abilities of his own.
This bodes terribly.
It appears our enemies
are the gods of the hill.
For the three rules she
broke, she lost three things.
She then further transgressed when
she begged for another chance.
Impudence.
On top of that, turning
someone into a book?
and reading their mind without permission!
is also an egregious act of disrespect!
Oh, no!
You're kidding!
This... this is bad!
My...
my chest!
It appears Miss Izumi is currently
suffering a heart attack.
Mr.
Rohan Kishibe,
you have broken one rule of etiquette,
and so you will lose one thing.
Tell me, do you intend
for her to die? You first.
Do you intend to continue with the trial,
or would you prefer to return home now?
You know I can't. Not anymore.
I won't leave her here.
Please, I beg of you, have mercy!
Her only transgression was
yearning for a chance at happiness!
I know now that when she said she wanted
to help me with my work, it was sincere.
Mercy is outside the realm of etiquette.
Here you will either gain,
or you will suffer loss.
Now, what is the proper
way to eat a cob of corn?
Well, would you care to
try once more, Mr. Kishibe?
Again, you are free to return
home whenever you wish.
Don't underestimate Rohan Kishibe.
The utensils you've
laid out here before me.
It is obvious that none of them
are suited for the task at hand.
Behold as I answer you!
Satisfied yet?
There's more.
You should brace yourself first, and
then look down when you're ready.
Who's the rule-breaker now?
I mean, I'll admit, this
isn't the plot I envisioned.
But given the tight deadline, it
was the best one I could write.
I'm speaking of my ability.
Heaven's door.
Oh, look.
You're doing it again.
It's both feet.
It's an impressive
power, wouldn't you say?
I do appreciate the lessons
you gave me. Thank you.
Now, on to the matter of what
I gain, as per the rules.
Seems my answer was right.
The proper way to eat a
cob of corn is by hand.
I think you owe my
colleague something as well.
Her beloved mother and boyfriend.
This is an obscene trick. You...
you will incur the wrath of the gods.
Mr.
Kishibe, will you be
making another attempt?
Or would you prefer to call it
a day and return home? My, my.
It seems the gods have no quarrel with me.
And why would they, considering
you're the one who violated the rules?
I choose to go home.
And I don't intend to return.
Wow, that's one heck of a story.
Oh yeah,
so do you know what ended up happening to
the editor lady's mother and boyfriend?
They were both perfectly fine.
They were merely rear-ended,
which panicked a relative,
who then proceeded to sound a false alarm.
That is such a relief.
By the way, Koichi, I have
some research to do after this,
and likely won't be back
until well after eight.
Okay.
So, you're gonna go do research, huh?
I hope you're looking up a way
to stop being a freeloader.
You make a very good point.
I should work on finding a new
place where I can draw freely.
Sadly, I'm utterly broke.
Do you want to come to my place?
We got plenty of rooms
you could set up in.
Huh?
That does sound nice.
As it happens, your father is
a topic of interest for me.
Wait, really?
You want to do today, then?
Maybe your heavens-whatever
can turn him back.
Could you try it?
I must refuse. What?
To chain a mystic rise.
I'm coming.
I'm on my way to find.
Eternal valedictives.
Exploding all their teardrops by the sun.
I can feel my heart feeling.
I can see my face.
All spinning round.
Beyond the storm.
Rise up to the sky.
Like a butterfly.
Show me what's inside.
Don't know the world grow.
Shining stars will guide me to.
Somewhere high.
Finding the truth.
Beyond the heaven storm.
Thank you.